Art and Architecture of China Slide Collection
Yale University Arts Library
- Republic of China/People's Republic (Box 27)
  - Artists: L (Box 28)
    - Lu Shoukun, 1919-1975 (Box 28)
    - Lu Yanshao, 1909- (Box 28)
  - Artists: M (Box 28)
    - Lu Yanshao, 1909- (Box 28)
  - Artists: N (Box 28)
    - Nie Ou, 1948- (Box 28)
  - Artists: P (Box 28)
    - Various Titles (Box 28)
    - Pan Tianshou, 1897-1971 [Slide boxes 164-165] (Box 28)
    - Peng Peichuan, 1941- [Slide box 165] (Box 28)
  - Artists: Q (Box 28)
    - Qi Baishi, 1863-1957 (Box 28)
    - Qian Songyan, 1898- (Box 28)
  - Artists: S (Box 28)
    - Various Titles (Box 28)
    - Shao Fei, 1954- (Box 28)
    - Shi Lu, 1919-1982 [Slide box 166] (Box 28)
    - Song Wenzhi, 1919- (Box 28)
  - Artists: T (Box 28)
    - Tang Yun, 1910- (Box 28)
    - Tseng Yu-Ho, 1923- (Box 28)
  - Artists: W (Box 28)
    - Various Titles (Box 28)
    - Wang-go HC Weng (Box 28)
    - Wang, CC, 1907- [Slide box 167] (Box 28)
    - Wang Guangyi, 1956- (Box 28)
    - Wang Jiqian (Box 28)
      Filed under CC Wang
    - Wang Wuxie, 1936- (Box 28)
    - Wang Zhen, 1867-1938 (Box 28)
    - Wu Changshuo, 1844-1927 (Box 28)
    - Wu Guanzhong, 1919- (Box 28)
    - Wu Zuoren, 1908- (Box 28)
  - Artists: X [Slide box 168] (Box 28)
    - Various Titles (Box 28)
    - Xiao Shufang, 1911- (Box 28)
    - Xie Zhilu, 1910- (Box 28)
    - Xu Beihong, 1895-1953 (Box 28)
  - Artists: Y (Box 28)
    - Ya Ming, 1924- (Box 28)
    - Yang Gang, 1946- (Box 28)
    - Yang Yanping, 1934- (Box 28)
    - Yu Youhan, 1943- (Box 28)
    - Yu Zhizhen (Box 28)
  - Artists: Z (Box 28)
    - Various Titles (Box 28)
    - Zhang Bu, 1934- (Box 28)
    - Zhao Xiuhuan, 1946- (Box 28)
    - Zhou Shaohua, 1929- (Box 28)
    - Zhao Shanqing, 1932- (Box 28)
    - Zhang Daqian (Box 28)
      Filed under Chang Dai-ch'ien
    - Zhu Qizhan, 1892- (Box 28)
- Photography (Box 29)
  [Slide box 169]
  - 20th century (Box 29)
    - Various Titles (Box 29)
- Prints (Box 29)
  - Artist Unknown (Box 29)
    - Various Titles (Box 29)
    - Gu-shi hua-pu (Box 29)
    - Western Buildings of Yuan Ming Yuan (Box 29)
    - Mustard Seed Garden Painting Manual (Box 29)
    - History of Chinese Woodcuts (Box 29)
      - Ancient Worthies (Drinking Cards) (Box 29)
      - Hsi-hsiang chi (Box 29)
      - Li-sao T'u (Box 29)
      - T'ai-yin Ta-ch'uan-chi [Slide box 170] (Box 29)
      - Ten Bamboo Studio Manual (Box 29)
      - Water Margin (Drinking Cards) (Box 29)
  - Known Artist (Box 29)
    - Ch'en Hung-shou, 1599-1632 (Box 29)
    - Hu Yeh Tsung (Box 29)
    - Kao Wen-chih (Box 29)
    - Lang Shih-ning, 1688-1768 (Box 29)
    - Wu Chün-fa (Box 29)
    - Xu Bing (Box 29)
- Sculpture (Box 29)
  - Prehistoric, -ca. 1550 BCE (Box 29)
  - Shang dynasty, ca. 1550-1030 BCE (Box 29)
  - Chou dynasty, 1030-222 BCE (Box 29)
    - Ceramic (Box 29)
    - Metal [Slide boxes 170-171] (Box 29)
    - Wood [Slide box 171] (Box 29)
  - Ch'in dynasty, 221-207 BCE (Box 29)
    - Qinshi Huangdi Mausoleum (Box 29)
  - Han dynasty, 206 BCE-220 CE (Box 29)
    - Ceramic (Box 29)
      - Various Titles (Box 29)
      - Architecture Models (Box 29)
      - Tiles [Slide boxes 171-172] (Box 29)
    - Metal [Slide box 172] (Box 29)
      - Various Titles (Box 29)
      - Flying Horse (Box 29)
    - Stone (Box 29)
      - Various Titles (Box 29)
      - Wu Liang Ci [Slide boxes 172-173] (Box 29)
      - Gao Yi Pillars [Slide box 173] (Box 29)
      - Ping Yang Pillars (Box 29)
      - Shen Pillars (Box 29)
      - Tomb of Huo Qubing (Box 29)
    - Wood (Box 29)
  - Six Dynasties, 221-581 (Box 29)
    - Ceramic (Box 29)
      - Various Titles (Box 29)
      - Nanking Tiles (Box 29)
      - Tombs (Box 29)
    - Metal [Slide box 174] (Box 29)
    - Stone (Box 29)
      - Animals (Box 29)
      - Caves (Box 29)
        - Lung-Men Caves, Honan (Box 29)
        - Pin-Yang Cave (Box 29)
        - Mai-Chi-Shan Caves, Kansu (Box 29)
        - Yun-Kang Caves, Shansi [Slide boxes 174-175] (Box 29)
          - Cave VI [Slide box 175] (Box 29)
      - Figures (Box 29)
      - Funerary Tablets (Mortuary) [Slide boxes 175-176] (Box 29–30)
      - Sarcophagi [Slide box 176] (Box 30)
      - Stelas (Box 30)
      - Tombs (Box 30)
        - An Jia Tomb, Xi'an (Box 30)
        - Fujia Tomb, Shandong Province [Slide boxes 176-177] (Box 30)
  - Sui dynasty, 581-618 [Slide box 177] (Box 30)
    - Various Titles (Box 30)
    - Miho Couch (Box 30)
    - Yu Hong Tomb, Shanxi Province (Box 30)
  - T'ang dynasty, 618-906 (Box 30)
    - Various Titles (Box 30)
    - Ceramic (Box 30)
      - Various Titles (Box 30)
      - Animals (Box 30)
      - Figures [Slide boxes 177-178] (Box 30)
    - Metal [Slide box 178] (Box 30)
    - Stone (Box 30)
      - Stone Various Titles (Box 30)
      - Lung-Men Caves, Honan (Box 30)
        - Various Titles (Box 30)
        - Feng-Hsien-Ssu (Cave XIX) (Box 30)
      - Yung-T'ai Tomb [Slide box 179] (Box 30)
  - Five Dynasties, 907-960 (Box 30)
  - Liao dynasty, 907-1125 (Box 30)
  - Sung dynasty, 960-1279 (Box 30)
    - Various Titles (Box 30)
    - Ceramic (Box 30)
    - Stone (Box 30)
      - Various Titles (Box 30)
      - Fo-Wan, Pei-Shan, Ta-Tsu-Hsien (Box 30)
    - Wood [Slide boxes 179-180] (Box 30)
  - Yuan dynasty, 1260-1368 [Slide box 180] (Box 30)
  - Ming dynasty, 1368-1644 (Box 30)
  - Ch'ing dynasty, 1644-1912 (Box 30)
  - Republic of China/People's Republic (Box 30)